(Are you sure you can be alone?)
(I’ll be fine, Pa.)
Surprise!
(Bay and I have been seeing each other for a while.)
- Can you come with me?
-To where?
If this doesn’t work,
you won’t have to see me again.
I’m begging you.
Can you let me live like a normal kid for a night?
Just don’t come home too late.
- What time is it now?
- What time is it?
10.59. Yes!
I said come home by 11 but you didn’t
have to wait until the last second.
Where are you staying tonight, Bay?
Uhh...
I can stay at my friend’s place, sir.
It’s late.
You can sleep with Sun tonight.
Pa!
Thank you, Pa.
Thank you so much…Pa.
I’m going to bed now.
Lock up for me.
Yes.
Are you crazy? My dad could see that.
Oh, he didn’t.
Just get in.
We’ll figure it out tomorrow.
Hey!
You’re taking the blanket all by yourself?
Fine, I’ll get another one.
Hey, don’t.
Use this one.
We can share it.
If you’re cold,
you can spoon me.
If you’re not cold, that’s fine.
But I am. So…let me spoon you.
Just like that?
(SAMING PHON FAI)
(SUPPORTED BY THE DEPARTMENT OF CULTURAL PROMOTION, MINISTRY OF CULTURE)
Ooh.
Pa’s famous Stir-fried Morning Glory.
- I can’t wait to try it.
- Eat up.
-I will.
-There’s omelet, too.
Here you go, boys.
Wow, Pa!
Are you feeding the whole block?
Well, I wasn’t sure how much I should make.
I’ve been living and eating alone lately.
Now there are two more people.
And you teenage boys must eat a lot, right?
That’s true, Pa. I always eat a lot when I’m home.
See? Bay loves to eat.
Come on. Let’s eat when it’s still hot.
- Here, Pa.
- Come on.
- Thank you, sir.
- Eat up, boy.
-Eat more.
-Pa, he gets more rice than I do.
- Here you go.
- Thank you, Pa.
Dig in, boys.
Hmm!
So delicious, Pa!
See?
- This is delicious.
- Good. Eat it up then.
I bet Bee doesn’t feed you this well.
Hey, Sun. The tryout for the national team
starts tomorrow, right?
Really?
- I’ll be there to support you then.
- Oh, please. There are four rounds.
You can come for the final round.
I’m sure I can make it.
Alright, Golden Boy.
But now you have to train and compete in the tryout, too.
Do you want to stay at the dorm instead?
Should be easier.
If that’s okay with you.
Staying at the dorm would be more convenient.
And I’ll come home on the weekends.
- Is that okay, Pa?
- Sure. I’m fine with that.
What about you, Bay?
If you’re still figuring it out,
you can stay with me.
- Right, Pa?
- Oh?
Let Bay stay with us.
What’s on your mind?
My stomach is burning.
Huh?
You guys have only fed me spicy food.
I usually eat something mild.
Like...
tofu and stuff.
But…don’t you miss your home?
I do.
I’m thinking about…
what I left at my house.
What…do you mean?
I left my computer,
my clothes,
- and some documents for my portfolio.
- Wait, wait ,wait.
Don’t you miss your dad at all?
Nah.
All I think about is…
how I will get my stuff without getting caught.
Where are you taking all this?!
Bay!
If you walk away, don’t ever come back again, you brat!
You stop seeing that boy right now!
Or else, don’t bother coming back here!
And I’m cutting you off, too!
If you’re so tough, get a job and feed yourself
Bee, can you get it together, huh?
Shut the f*ck up, Chun!
Your son has a bad influence on my son, bastard!
- Hey, hey, hey. Don’t talk about my son!
- Pa. Pa.
Come on!
Pa, enough.
Pa, get in the house.
Come on and finish this, Chun!
Are you a coward?
You can’t face me, coward?!
You pick up all his junk!
Take this, too!
You take it all!
Brats!
Don’t you want to call your mom at least?
She must be busy taking care of my grandma.
She wouldn’t want to hear about this thing.
But this is not just something Bay.
This is a big deal.
I don’t want other people to worry about me.
Don’t say that, Bay.
No matter what it is,
you can talk to me about it.
You don’t have to carry this on your shoulders, Bay.
I’m here for you, always.
Or should we call Boat instead?
Boat must be busy right now.
It’s okay.
I’ll call him myself.
Hello.
Hello, Boat.
This is Sun.
Yeah. What’s going on?
Is there something wrong?
Well...
Bay is having trouble with his dad.
Why? What happened?
Why didn’t you call me?
Mom!
I left you guys alone for a few months.
What happened to this family, huh?
Boat,
why didn’t you tell me about all of this?
And you are no better.
Whenever I called to check on you guys,
you said everything’s fine.
Does this look fine to you?
It’s these two who ruined our family’s reputation.
Isn’t it because you made Boat lie about being an intern
- just so you could brag about it to Sun’s family?
- Bay!
And you wouldn’t even let me and Sun be friends
because you just couldn’t get out of your stupid way!
- Bay, don’t you speak to me that way!
- Why can’t I?
Why would you drag us all into this?
Why, Dad?
Do you even realize that this is all your fault?
Bay, it’s not your dad’s fault.
I don’t know if he stole their recipe or not, Mom.
But opening a dim sum shop across from his place,
someone he used to call friend.
What kind of person does that?!
If you don’t know anything, shut
your mouth, Bay!
You don’t know what I had to do to take care of this family!
But using your own struggles
as an excuse to treat their family badly…
Do you think that’s right, Dad?!
Don’t you walk away, Bay.
Come back and apologize to me!
- Bay!!
- Bay, come back!
Bay!
Bay, come back!
- Bay! Bay, don’t go!
- Mom, mom. I’ll go after him. Don’t worry.
Thank you so much, Coach,
for telling us Bay was here.
Hey.
I’m sorry
for not picking up the phone.
It’s okay.
For earlier,
I want to apologize, too.
About what?
I don’t know.
Whenever Dad tried to guilt trip you,
I wasn’t able to defend you.
Now I really know how it feels
to be hated by my own father.
I’d like to properly thank you
for taking care of Bay.
It’s nothing. Don’t worry about it.
Mom.
- Bay.
- Mom.
Where have you been?
I’m so sorry, Mom.
I’m sorry, too, for not knowing about this sooner.
Bay, do you want to stay with me at Grandma’s?
I’d like to stay with Sun, Mom.
That’s fine.
But don’t forget to call me, okay?
I will, Mom.
(Call me or Boat if you need anything?)
What are you doing?
And where did you get this?
I stole it from our prom night.
Thought it was kinda cute.
I liked it.
I just didn’t know how to cheer you up.
Why are you so cute?
Just staying by my side
and being cute like this is enough.
Or you can take your shirt off.
-I like it when you’re half naked.
-You perv.
Hey, I thought you wanted to cheer me up.
No, I’m done.
Hey, your boyfriend is feeling down.
Hey, what was that? I didn’t see it.
-Let me see. Please, I’d like to see more.
-Haven’t you seen enough already?
-Let me see. I wanna see.
-That’s enough.
Let me see.
Let’s go.
I’m off to school, Dad.
-See you.
I’ll meet you at the dorm, okay?
I’m off. Bye-bye.
Pa.
Seeing their family fight because Bay and I are together,
I can’t help but feel guilty, Pa.
Now that your dad’s cut you off,
will he pay for your tuition in Italy?
No.
But I’d still like to see if I’m qualified.
If I am, that means one day
I might figure out how to get there on my own.
-Hello
-Morning, guys.
-Good morning.
Hi, Bay. Hi, Petong.
How are you holding up, Bay?
I haven’t told you anything.
Everyone on Discord knows what happened.
Are you okay now?
Mmm, I’m okay, I guess.
-Not okay. This is not okay.
-We’re here for you, okay?
Bay-Sun fandom is here for you as well.
Nice.
And your fans got you something.
Over there, that’s your food support.
Wow! You’ve got lots of support, huh?
You can take it all home, Bay.
Okay, okay.
I call dips on orange cake.
It’s all mine.
-Don’t eat it all by yourself.
-Let me have some. Come on
Fine.
Thanks a lot for keeping an eye on Bay.
Oh, that’s not a big deal.
Just seeing Bay and Sun together makes me really happy.
The only problem now is your dad.
Oh, no.
-Hey, are you alright?
-My bad.
-Hey.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I’m so so sorry.
It’s fine.
Are you okay?
I’m okay.
I should ask you if you’re okay.
You were quite absent-minded.
Nothing. I was just…
thinking about the past.
You remember Ming?
Ming…
Sun’s brother? Why?
We were so close back then.
But since our fathers had a fight,
we’ve never looked at each other again.
I pushed myself so hard to get into medical school.
So my dad could brag about it to their family.
But did that change anything?
It didn’t.
I do love my dad.
But it’s so hard to live with him.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Can I give you a hug?
Thank you.
Boat, you did your best, okay?
Today is the first round of the qualifiers.
We’ll go from 32 players down to 16.
The winner of each match will advance
and return for the second round next Thursday.
It’s a single-elimination format,
with the final round taking place on February 20.
FEBRUARY 2026
We’re selecting five players to represent the Thai national team,
along with three reserve players.
Understand?
Yes.
Bay,
Next week, after Chinese New Year, the national team tryouts.
Hey!
My boyfriend is going national now?
And after Chinese New Year,
I think I’m going home.
Wanna come with me?
Don’t look sad.
You can stay with me,
so you won’t be lonely.
Peek-a-boo!
Well? Are you coming now?
Alright, alright. I’m coming.
Five seconds.
Just five?
-Ten seconds.
-Five!
-Eight!
-Six!
-Seven?
-Six, final offer.
Deal.
-Deal.
Ready?
You sure?
-One, two, three, four, five, six.
-Hey! That was too fast!
Hey, open up!
Are you challenging me?
SAMING PHON FAI
-Pa!
-Wacth out!
That was loud.
Guys, come on and eat. Come on.
Come on, come on.
That was loud.
CLOSE DURING CHINESE NEW YEAR
FEBRUARY 17-19
Are you okay?
I thought I’d moved on.
But seeing my house being so quiet like this…kinda makes me sad.
I get it.
Do you think my dad will ever accept us?
Maybe one day he will.
Look at my dad. Even he could come around and accept you.
Seeing their family fight because
Bay and I are together,
I can’t help but feel guilty, Pa.
Sun,
this is not your fault.
It’s my fault and Bee’s fault.
Even if you boys broke up,
it wouldn’t make us stop fighting.
You’ve seen this before,
with Ming and Boat.
They stopped being friends
and wouldn’t even look at each other.
But that didn’t make anything better.
Pa.
I’m so sorry
that it took me this long to realize
how badly Bee and I hurt all of you.
I guess it will take Bee some time
to realize it, too.
I should know. It took me long enough.
I think people in their 50s
still have their own coming-of-age moments.
Hopefully, he’ll come around.
Are you hungry?
Wanna eat with us?
Are you sure?
Come on.
Pa has prepared a huge feast.
There are like 5-6 menus.
So many dishes. Eat a lot, guys.
We’re here.
Oh, Sun. Come on and eat, boys.
Nice to meet you.
And who is this boy?
This is Bay.
Bay?
Is he the son of the man you had a problem with?
Yes.
But now…
Bay and Sun are boyfriends.
Bay.
Yes, ma’am?
You must have done something right.
Even us, Chun’s siblings couldn’t do it.
We’ve been trying to get him to let go of...
the whole stealing-recipe thing for a long time.
But this one never listened.
You two did a great job getting him
to change his mind.
Now Chun is like a different person.
Great job, boys.
For you.
Thank you.
You get one, too.
Thank you, ma’am.
Now let’s eat, guys.
-Come on, boys.
-Let us eat.
-So many dishes.
-Let’s dig in.
Ma!
Pa, hello.
Didn’t know you guys were coming.
Sun called and invited us.
Are you okay with that?
Yes, of course.
Come have a seat.
-Good to see you.
-Come and sit.
Hello, everyone.
-Nice to see you.
-Hello. Hello.
-Hello. Have a seat.
I guess…
we’re gonna need more food.
-Come on. Come help me in the kitchen.
-Oh, sure.
-Let’s go.
-We’ll be back.
-You guys eat. I’ll be right back.
-Yes, thank you.
-Make a lot more, Auntie.
-Alright.
This isn’t enough.
Let’s get the rice.
Try this, my aunt’s duck recipe.
So good.
-You like it?
-Yeah, it’s good.
Told you.
-You have some, too.
-Okay.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Hmmm.
A big piece of chicken. This is for you.
Papa, have some Hoi Jo.
Good evening.
Bay.
Mom.
SAMING PHON FAI
OPEN DAILY
I bought you some Pad Mee, here.
Thank you.
Eat up.
Coach Kong, what are you doing here?
I go where the food goes.
As good as always.
Go talk to him.
Ming.
Go talk to Boat.
I have to speak with your dad.
Sun.
Yes?
Can I ask you something?
Boat and Ming… What are they?
Hmm, what do you mean?
I mean...
Are they like you and Bay?
Are they fighting but actually liking each other?
How would I know?
If you want to know, you should go find out.
If they seem to have feelings for each other,
you shut it down.
Period.
You’re right.
I should have thought of that. I’ll be back.
Are you insane?
Just go, Coach.
Don’t waste your time talking about it. Go.
-Just go.
-I’m eating.
Go, Coach, go.
How’ve you been? Are you doing okay?
Mmm, I’m doing fine.
How long has it been since we talked
to each other?
I didn’t even know how you were doing.
Of course you didn’t.
Look at what our dads have done.
Anyway…
I’m sorry.
I shouldn’t have listened to my dad.
I was your best friend but I didn’t do anything about it.
I still regret it to this day.
You don’t have to.
You and I can still become friends again.
I’m sorry, man.
Ahem!
What? Can’t I hug him?
It was a friendly hug.
I didn’t say anything, okay?
It was just a friendly, very friendly hug.
We’re friends, see?
Do whatever you want with your friend.
Kong, Boat, wait for me in the car.
I need a minute.
Okay, Mom.
Honey.
Wait.
Just apologize to your sons.
You want me to apologize?
You know what I’ve done for this family.
Have they ever appreciated their father?
Stop using that as an excuse.
It was my fault.
You should blame me.
I’m sorry.
-Mom.
-Hmm?
I already know the truth
about our family stealing Chun’s dim sum recipe.
I’ve never tasted Chun’s dim sum before.
I knew right away when I tasted it.
It tasted so similar to dad’s.
Too similar.
It was my fault we were in debt.
I pressured you so much that you had to do such a thing .
Okay, hold on a second.
SAMING PHON FAI
Hurry. Come help me, quick.
Here, thank you so much.
Here, two pork buns and two cream buns. Thank you.
I’ll have one mantou and one BBQ pork bun, please.
-Okay. You, make more. We’re almost out.
-Yes, sir.
What was your order again?
Honey.
MORTGAGES ACCEPTED FOR HOUSES AND LAND
We’ll get through this.
It was all my fault.
I let you do that to your friend.
I could have stopped you
but I didn’t do anything.
-We didn’t do anything wrong.
-I let all this happen.
None of us did anything wrong.
I didn’t take Chun’s recipe
and you don’t have to feel guilty.
-Bee.
-Damn.
Bee!
Bay, are you with your dad?
I don’t know where he went.
Thank you
for making me feel at home today.
♪ You’re the only one I’ll ever give a Like ♪
♪ Want, want you to come and be a part of my life ♪
♪ Morning, afternoon, or all night,
I’ll always make you smile ♪
♪ No matter how many seconds pass,
I promise I’ll never make you cry ♪
♪ I’ll hold you tight ♪
♪ Never let you out of my sight ♪
♪ Stay by my side ♪
TODAY, FEBRUARY 20, NATIONAL TEAM TRYOUT
You are so adorable.
Hey!
You should adore me then.
I adore you.
We should’ve started dating when we were eight
so we had more time together before I leave.
You go do what you love over there.
And I’ll do what I love over here.
Bay!
I don’t think I can do this, Coach.
Bay is in good hands. Don’t worry.
While I’m gone, just remember I’m coming back for you.
SUPPORTED BY THE DEPARTMENT OF CULTURAL PROMOTION,
MINISTRY OF CULTURE